perfectdone.com 2010-06-20

# 

## Privacy Policy

Perfectdone.com (the "Site") respects your privacy. Here's our privacy policy for this Site:

### Personally Identifiable Information

The Site will not provide our advertisers or anyone else outside the Site with any information specific to you collected from the Site unless we have your consent. The only Site employees or consultants allowed access to personal information about you are those who need to have access. Any employee or consultant who violates our privacy and security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination or prosecution.

### What Information is Collected and Used:

We will not release your name, e-mail address or any other personal information to anyone else outside the Site unless we have your consent. However, we may disclose your personal information if (i) required to do so by law, court order or subpoena, or as requested by other government, law enforcement, or investigative authority, (ii) we in good faith believe that such disclosure is necessary or advisable, including without limitation to protect the rights or properties of the Site, (iii) we have reason to believe that disclosing your personal information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, or has breached an agreement, or if anyone else could be harmed by such activities or interference, (iv) if we determine an ad posted violates our terms of use or the rights of a third party, or (v) there is an emergency involving personal danger.

Please note that if you post any of your personal information on the Site, such information may be collected and used by others over whom the Site has no control. The Site is not responsible for the use by third parties of information you post or otherwise make public.

### Cookies

"Cookies" are small text files that allow Web sites to store and retrieve information about you from your computer system. The Site does serve cookies to track individual site usage for later aggregation. But we do not use cookies in order to retrieve any information from your computer other than information originally sent in a Site cookie, such as a user code. We have no control over whether and how our advertisers use cookies that originate from their website.

### Communication from the Site

From time to time, we may send you information with announcements and updates about the Site and your account. You may elect to opt-out of ongoing e-mail communication from us, such as newsletters, subscriptions, account information, promotional materials, contest results, survey inquiries, etc. by using a simple "opt out" procedure. You need only reply to the communication with the word "unsubscribe" (without the quotation marks) in the body of your e-mail response and your name will be removed from that mailing list. However, if you opt-out of receiving our announcements and updates about your account, you may no longer have access to areas restricted to account members.

### Correction/Update of Personal Information:

If your personal information changes, you may review/correct/update your personal information previously provided at any time by clicking [here](http://www.perfectdone.com/contact.php) and sending us an email. You may also have your personal profile data deleted from our database by contacting us [here](http://www.perfectdone.com/contact.php). However, if you have your personal profile data deleted from our database, you may forfeit entrance rights to areas restricted to account members and certain benefits for account members.

### Children

The Site is not intended for children under the age of 13 nor does the Site knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. The Site does not orient this Site toward children or target them as an audience, nor does it screen them from using the Site. Some of the material on this Site is for mature audiences, and parents and guardians should take responsibility for monitoring their children's use. The Site does not collect or distribute information indicating whether a user is a child.

### Links to Other sites

This Site provides links and pointers to Web sites maintained by other organizations. The Site provides these links as a convenience to users, but it does not operate, control or endorse such sites. The Site also disclaims any responsibility for the information on those sites and any products or services offered there, and cannot vouch for the privacy policies of such sites. The Site does not make any warranties or representations that any linked sites (or even this Site) will function without error or interruption, that defects will be corrected, or that the sites and their servers are free of viruses and other problems that can harm your computer.

### E-Commerce and Our Secure Server

All commerce transactions that take place on this site are processed through our secure server in order to make every reasonable effort to insure that your personal information is protected. Any transactions that take place on other sites that have link from our site are not necessarily handled in this fashion. The Site disclaims any responsibility for transactions conducted on those sites and cannot vouch for the security of the information submitted in those transactions.

### Policy Changes and Acceptance

This privacy policy is effective as of July 1, 2007. By using our Site and its services, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Policy, you may discontinue use of our Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of any portion of our Site following notification or posting of such changes will constitute your acceptance of these changes.

### More Questions?

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, e-mail them by clicking [here](http://www.perfectdone.com/contact.php), and be sure to indicate the specific site you're visiting and the nature of your question or concern.
